<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Services on Rajware Services Pvt. Ltd.</title><link>https://www.rajware.net/services/</link><description>Recent content in Services on Rajware Services Pvt. Ltd.</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 16:46:52 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.rajware.net/services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Training</title><link>https://www.rajware.net/services/training/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 16:46:43 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://www.rajware.net/services/training/</guid><description>We believe that to use any techonology effectively, you have to understand the motivation behind its creation, and its basic design. All our training programs are built around these two ideas. We also believe that the best way to learn a technology is to use it. Thus, all our trainings are hands-on. After a initial section where we discuss the motivation of any technology, the rest of the training is completely practical.</description></item><item><title>Consulting</title><link>https://www.rajware.net/services/consulting/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 16:46:47 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://www.rajware.net/services/consulting/</guid><description>We provide consulting services to product and service-oriented organizations, in the specific areas of project scoping, design and architecture review, application performance and scaling, and team capabality. We can engage tactically or strategically, as per need.
Strategic Engagement We work with clients to identify, assess and build approaches as per specific business needs. To this effect, we:
conduct workshops to identify problems, desired outcomes, and technology fits identify and evaluate champions or teams build team capabilities and practices manage development of proof-of-concept projects provide ongoing support as required Tactical Engagement We can also engage directly with delivery teams for specific, short-term deliverables.</description></item><item><title>Open Source</title><link>https://www.rajware.net/services/open-source/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 16:46:52 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://www.rajware.net/services/open-source/</guid><description>We strongly believe in Open Source. Most of our training courses are built on open-source technologies such as Docker, Kubernetes, Helm, Go, and so on.
Our standard course content, as well as tools that we have built to deliver these courses, are all available under the MIT License on Github.
We spun off a tool that we originally built as an aid to our Kubernetes work as an independent open-source project called kuttiproject.</description></item></channel></rss>